He's the doctor's assistant, right?
那个医生的助手…是吗
Well, where did my agent go?
是说 我家的特务是跑去哪里了啦
He seems to have been abandoned.
完全就是被抛弃的样子
Rest in peace.
愿他安息
His expression is truly miserable.
好凄惨的表情
-Who are you? -What?
-你是哪位 -咦
We have met on the bus.
是我啊，我们有在巴士上见过…
You're the grave digger.
啊 你是那个挖坟的
That's a bit rude.
讲得也太难听了吧
At least call me a tomb raider.
至少说我是盗墓人吧
Things are pretty bad here too.
这里也很不得了呢
Oh my.
真是的
Well then, I take my leave first.
那么 我就先告辞了
Well, do you know where to find her?
咦 你知道要去哪里吗
Who are you referring to?
你是指什么
Your partner.
你的搭档
Why would you know?
你怎么会知道
I accidentally saw her.
我是不小心瞄到的
Come with me. I'll take you there.
跟我来吧 我带你去
(Metallic Rouge)
《金属口红》
Good morning, Rouge Redstar.
早安啊 露琼・雷德斯塔
Sorry I scared you.
抱歉吓到你了
Just go back to sleep.
你就继续沉睡吧
My beloved Rouge.
我心爱的露琼
What a spectacular music.
很美妙的曲子
Right, Rouge?
没错吧 露琼
Spectacular…
美妙…
What does it mean?
什么是美妙
That means something you'd feel small after you play it.
表示这是首弹奏之后 会觉得自己很渺小的曲子
It's a song your mother and I loved. She's the one who made you.
是我和制造出你的母亲 所喜欢的曲子
Mother?
母亲…
Father and brother, why don't you have to inject this?
父亲和哥哥为什么不用注射这个呢
Because there is no need.
因为没有必要
We can eat this together.
这个的话 就能一起吃了
It's delicious.
好好吃哦
Deform.
变形
Happy Birthday.
生日快乐
Happy Birthday, Rouge.
生日快乐 露琼
Rouge.
露琼
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
My poor beloved daughter.
我可怜的爱女
You couldn't escape it from birth.
你打从一出生就无法逃离那里
Amazing!
好厉害
So where is she?
所以在哪里
I think she's somewhere nearby.
可能…在那里吧
Tell me you didn't bring me here by relying on that little information.
你该不会只凭这点资讯 就把我带来这里吧
Really?
真的还假的啊
We have to find a way to get in there.
必须要想办法进去里面才行
Then we have to break the ceiling.
这样只能打破天花板了吧
I would never be that savage.
我才不会那么野蛮呢
Please let us in.
请让我们通过
How did you do that?
你是怎么办到的
Bribery.
贿赂
Don't be fooled by its look.
别看它这个样子
It is actually a key.
其实是钥匙
War machine.
战争机器
They are indeed in cahoots with the Usurpers.
果然和篡夺者有挂勾
Usurpers.
篡夺者…
Junoid.
由诺伊德
Knowing that name means you're no ordinary person.
知道这个名字 表示你不是等闲之辈呢
What?
什么
Forget it, we all have secrets.
算了 各有原由嘛
Then I'm off.
那我走了
Where are you going?
你要去哪里
I will do what I should do.
做我的老本行
This place is full of treasures.
这里可是宝库呢
Eden Varock.
啊 伊甸・维洛克
What?
什么
My name.
我的名字
Bang.
砰
Do you like music?
你喜欢音乐吗
I don't know.
我也不知道…
But I think I do.
但应该算是喜欢吧
What does it mean?
这是什么意思
I heard a song once.
以前我有听过一首曲子
What kind of song was it?
是什么样的曲子
What's wrong?
您怎么了
I know this song.
我知道这首曲子
But I don't like it.
但我不喜欢
It reminds me of people I dislike.
会让我想起讨厌的人们
Why did you kill me?
为什么要杀我
A Nean cannot kill another Nean.
涅安无法杀死涅安
Fratricide Rouge.
同胞杀手露琼
Nean Traitor Rouge.
涅安叛徒露琼
I'll take you to the next target.
带您前往下一个目标
Nice to meet you.
请多指教
I am Gene Junghardt,
我是吉恩・容格哈特
your brother.
是你的哥哥
What is your name?
你叫什么名字
Rouge.
露琼…
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
Rouge,
露琼
the Ruby Star.
红宝石之星
I'll take you to the next target.
带您前往下一个目标
A SPACE VOYAGE WITH NO ESCAPE
(无路可逃的太空之旅)
Fratricide Rouge.
同胞杀手露琼
Nean Traitor Rouge.
涅安叛徒露琼
A Nean can't kill humans.
涅安无法杀人
Don't kill humans.
不能杀人
Can't kill humans.
无法杀人
It is Code Eve.
是CODE EVE…
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
-Don't kill humans. -It is Code Eve.
-不能杀人 -是CODE EVE…
-Can't kill humans.
-无法杀人
(Episode 5: Carnival Dances with Lost Memories)
(5 嘉年华乃遗忘与舞动)
Come on, take it.
来 拿去吧
Is that one related to the Usurpers?
那是与篡夺者有关连的人吗
The target's id has been found.
发现目标的伊德
Then I need to find that kid.
再来就是要找出那位小朋友了…
It hurts.
好痛…
They are the negative legacy of our father.
他们是父亲的…负之遗产
Negative legacy?
负之遗产…
The negative legacy must be eradicated.
负之遗产必须彻底铲除
That's the father's wish.
那就是父亲的愿望
Exactly.
没错
And they're the ones who took our father's life.
而且就是他们夺走了父亲的性命
The Immortal Nine who killed our father
杀死父亲的不朽九人
is unforgivable.
不可原谅
It must be done by us.
要由我们兄妹俩来完成
The two of us have to avenge our father.
由我们两人来为父亲报仇
This is a classified mission.
这是机密任务
We absolutely cannot…
绝对不能…
Let anyone know.
让任何人知道
You should know it.
你应该知道
I should know it.
应该…知道
You know it.
你知道
I know it.
我…知道
What's wrong with Code Eve?
CODE EVE怎么了
Where is Code Eve
CODE EVE…
on you?
在你的哪里
The Immortal Nine is a group of Neans with special powers.
不朽九人 是一群拥有特殊能力的涅安
They are the parents of numerous Neans,
他们为众多涅安之父母
and also their matrix.
亦为其母体
Though they have been silent for a long time,
虽沉寂已久
now, they have started to act again.
但如今却再次开始行动
They hate humans.
他们憎恨着人类
Your father was killed when trying to stop them.
你的父亲则是为了阻止他们 而惨遭杀害
Their target is Code Eve.
目标是CODE EVE
If Code Eve is released, the world will change.
解放CODE EVE的话 世界将会产生变革
Change…
变革…
Let the two of us complete what our father could not.
由我跟你两人 来完成父亲未能完成之事吧
Rouge.
露琼
But…
可是…
Sarah didn't seem to be a bad person.
莎拉看起来不像是坏人
Afdal.
阿夫戴尔…
He looked miserable too.
看起来也很痛苦
He was concerned about Neans in trouble.
他心系于困苦的涅安
He looked so upset.
感觉很难过
So, do we have to defeat them?
即便如此 也必须要打倒他们吗
Yes.
没错
Why?
为什么
No reason.
不为什么
Who
你…
are you?
是谁
I'm a Puppetmaster.
操偶师
What have you done to me?
你对我做了什么
My job is to collect pitiful puppets
我的工作是收集可怜的人偶
and help them.
并帮助他们
Are you saying I am a pitiful puppet?
你是说我是可怜的人偶吗
Aren't you?
不是吗
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
And you are also lovable beings.
而你也同时是惹人怜爱的存在
So I have to cut that thread.
所以我要切断那条线
Cut the cursed thread that has been manipulating you.
切断那条你毫无察觉 在不知不觉间操纵着你的诅咒丝线
That's what I'm doing.
这就是我在做的事
What will I be like when you're done?
完成之后我会变成什么样子
You will be free.
你将会得到自由
What happens to me when I'm free?
得到自由后我会如何
You can be yourself.
能够成为自己
Myself?
自己…
Be yourself,
不是别人的自己
not someone else.
也就是真实的自我
Can you be yourself?
你是自己吗
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
Are you free?
你是自由的吗
Go find it out yourself.
你就亲身去找出那个答案吧
Go wherever you want to.
去吧 想去哪就去哪
And then go look for it.
然后去寻找吧
Find it.
将它找出来
Can you be yourself
你究竟是自己
or just a pitiful puppet?
还是具可怜的人偶
Find that answer.
找出那个答案吧
How?
要怎么找…
I have done my job
我已完成了该行之事
and get what I need.
拿到了必要之物
I am free.
我是自由的
Brother.
哥哥
Let me introduce you.
向你介绍一下
This is my sister.
这位是我的妹妹
Hey.
喂
Wake up. What's wrong with you?
醒醒 怎么了
This is…
这里是…
We are inside the moving carnival.
移动嘉年华的内部
What happened?
发生什么事了
It's a long story.
说来话长…
Hey.
嘿咻
I get what I need.
我拿到了必要之物
I have heard this somewhere.
这句话好像在哪里听过
Anyway, let's get out of here.
总之先离开这里吧
You're lighter than I thought.
你比我想象得还轻呢
Could you return that thing?
可以请您把东西还来吗
I'm not as generous as the leader.
我可没有团长那么宽宏大量
I'm sorry that I can't do as you told.
这个有点恕难从命
That's a pity.
那还真是遗憾
I smell the same thing on you as I do.
我在您的身上闻到与我相同的味道
Really?
是吗
I don't wear perfume of Usurpers.
我可没擦过篡夺者牌的香水耶
Thank you all for coming today.
感谢各位今天的莅临
Our troupe is stationed on many planets and travels through various galaxies,
本团在许多星球驻留 航行于各个星系
providing fun and exciting performances to countless guests.
为无数客人提供欢乐与兴奋的表演
However,
然而事出突然
our event has to end today.
本团于本地的活动将于今天结束
Thank you all.
感谢各位…
If the threads of fate meet somewhere in the future,
如果命运的丝线 会在未来某处交会的话
please come and enjoy our performance.
届时还请拨冗前来欢赏本团的表演
Thank you all.
感谢各位…
Look forward to seeing you again.
那么以后有缘再相逢
Goodbye, everyone.
各位再见…
Headquarters has asked us to return.
总部发出了召回命令
I just got here. What does this mean?
我人才刚到这里 到底是什意思
Maybe your application was not filled out properly.
会不会是申请书没有填妥
What?
哪里没填妥
I made it all up.
那全都是我乱写的
Please don't tell the truth to the headquarters.
还请您别跟总部实话实说…
What's wrong?
怎么了
I don't know.
不晓得
Probably we are heading to another planet.
可能是要前往别的星球吧
Our leader acts on his whims.
我们团长可是阴晴不定的
Can you be yourself?
你是自己吗
It hurts.
好痛…
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
Go.
去吧
Go wherever you want to.
想去哪就去哪
What's wrong with you?
你是怎么了
I want to save you.
我想要救你
You should worry about yourself.
你还是多担心自己一点吧
You can do this without deforming.
没变形就能如此…
Impressive.
有一套
Gladiator.
斗士…
As many as cockroaches.
跟蟑螂一样…
I guess I have to do it in a savage way, right?
我想也只能用 这种野蛮的方法了对吧
Hey, what do you see?
喂 你看到什么
Looks like the red guy and the lady from the Aletheia.
似乎是红色家伙 和那位真理部的女性
How is it? I was right, wasn't I?
怎么样 我猜得没错吧
Your intuition again?
又是直觉吗
Are you alright?
你还好吗
The wind is strong, and sand gets into my eyes.
风很大 沙子还飞到眼睛里
I'm far from the ground.
离地面又很远
I'm not alright.
其实没有很好
Don't think about running away.
你别想逃
No.
不
I have to.
我要逃
I'm really sorry.
实在非常抱歉
She has taken Verde's id.
维杜的伊德被抢走了
This is fate, the rule of the world.
这也是命运使然 世界的定理
We were destined to lose that thing.
我们命中注定失去那个东西
Anyway, I get what I need.
无论如何 我得到了必要之物
Go, just go.
去吧 尽管去吧
Rouge Redstar.
露琼・雷德斯塔
We'll meet again one day,
终有一天 我们会再相见的
when you are truly free.
在你得到真正的自由之时
Thank you for your work.
辛苦了
Hmm.
嗯
What happened?
发生什么事了
I don't quite remember.
我不太记得了
My memory is so foggy. I think I saw something weird.
模模糊糊的 总觉得好像看到了什么怪东西
It seems nice to do that once in a while.
偶尔这样好像也不错
I always save you,
每次都是我去救你
and you saved me this time.
这次变成被你所救
No.
不…
You saved me.
是你救了我
I just happened to meet you.
我只是碰巧遇到你而已
You came to save me.
你来救我了
So I wanted to save you.
所以我才会想要救你
No.
不…
But I wish I could be saved in a safer way.
不过我还是希望 能被人更加平安地救下来呢
Who exactly are they?
他们到底是什么人啊
What is certain is that they are interested in you.
能确定的是他们对你有兴趣
Did they do something unpleasant to you?
你有被他们做了什么吗 比如说奇怪的事之类的
You're disgusting.
恶心…
Sorry.
抱歉
Besides,
还有啊
that black guy…
那个黑色家伙…
I'm actually pretty savage too.
我其实也是挺野蛮的
Miss.
小姐